[
    {
        "id":0,
        "question": "Which one is the smallest ocean in the World?" ,
        "options":[
            "Indian",
            "Pacific",
            "Atlantic",
            "Arctic"
        ],
        "answer": "Arctic"
    },
    {
        "id":1,
        "question": "Which country gifted the Statue of Liberty to USA in 1886?" ,
        "options":[
            "France",
            "Canada",
            "Brazil",
            "England"
        ],
        "answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "id":2,
        "question": "Dead Sea is located between which two countries?" ,
        "options":[
            "Jordan and Sudan",
            "Jordan and Israel",
            "Turkey and UAE",
            "UAE and Egypt"
        ],
        "answer": "Jordan and Israel"
    },
    {
        "id":3,
        "question": "In which ocean Bermuda Triangle region is located?" ,
        "options":[
            "Indian",
            "Pacific",
            "Atlantic",
            "Arctic"
        ],
        "answer": "Atlantic"
    },
    {
        "id":4,
        "question": "Which country is also known as the Land of Rising Sun?" ,
        "options":[
            "Japan",
            "New Zealand",
            "Fiji",
            "China"
        ],
        "answer": "Japan"
    },
    {
        "id":5,
        "question": "Which country is known as the Land of Thunderbolts?" ,
        "options":[
            "China",
            "Bhutan",
            "Mangolia",
            "Thailand"
        ],
        "answer": "Bhutan"
    },
    {
        "id":6,
        "question": "Which continent has the highest number of countries?" ,
        "options":[
            "Asia",
            "Europe",
            "Africa",
            "North America"
        ],
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "id":7,
        "question": "In which country, white elephant is found?" ,
        "options":[
            "India",
            "Sri Lanka",
            "Thailand",
            "Malaysia"
        ],
        "answer": "Thailand"
    },
    {
        "id":8,
        "question": "Total number of oceans in the World is?" ,
        "options":[
            "3",
            "5",
            "7",
            "12"
        ],
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "id":9,
        "question": "Which country is also known as the Land of Thousand Lakes?" ,
        "options":[
            "Iceland",
            "Norway",
            "Finland",
            "Switzerland"
        ],
        "answer": "Finland"
    }

]